WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
- Audiorecordings
  - Pollution Special, wsyr_radio_585; note on box reads: "For radio airing at 8:05 PM, Mon. April 27, total time without break 22:03, before break: 19:19, after: 30:49"; note on reel reads: "Toscanini, 9/3/44, Mozart Symphony No. 29".; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 22:03 (Box 22)
  - Portion of E. B. Browning’s "Sonnets from the Portuguese" by Alan Milair, wsyr_radio_634; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Portion of President Roosevelt Speech in French with translation; One Man’s Family, part 2 Red Ch 2 BK 44, 11/07/1942; wsyr_radio_018; Inside - Easy Washer Interview (aborted), Middle Two - Esso Reporter; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 6)
    A- "One man's family", chapter 2, book 44 (part 2), wartime theme announcer Ken Carpenter; B-1 Easy Washer, wartime shortages. Interview of John Dyer, Easy Washer engineer; 2-ESSO Reporter (out take); 3-ESSO sell scrap - keep best for yourself, turn household scrap in to gouverment driver. ESSO reporter -out tro; 4 President Roosevelt speaks French, Re: Invasion Africa
  - Premier of "Doctor Doolittle" at the Kallet Shoppingtown Theater, wsyr_radio_628; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
    Floyd Ottoway and Kay Russell, Kallet Shoppingtown Theater, Broadway at Night program "Doctor Doolittle" premiere in Syracuse
  - Presentation of Newspaper files to Onondaga Historical Association, 01/30/1950; wsyr_radio_053; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 9)
    A-Presentation of Syracuse Newspaper archive (1839-1949) to the Onondaga Historical Association (OHA) by WSYR. Elliot Gove, Col. Harry, C. Wilder, E. R. Vadeboneouer, Alan Kauflan, OHA President, Major Harry C. Darston, OHA Secretary
  - President Comacho, President Roosevelt (part 1); Richard Harkness news, 04/20/1943; wsyr_radio_199; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Comacho, President Roosevelt (part 2); Richard Harkness news, 04/20/1943; wsyr_radio_200; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Dwight D Eisenhower Speech, Farm., 04/16/1956; 04/19/1956; wsyr_radio_035; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 6)
  - President Eisenhower Address at Governor’s Conference, parts 1 and 2, Seattle WA, 08/04/1953; wsyr_radio_069; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 11)
  - President Eisenhower at Columbia University (part 3), 06/01/1954; wsyr_radio_421; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower at Columbia University (parts 1 and 2), 06/01/1954; wsyr_radio_420; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower Boston Garden Speech, 09/21/1953; wsyr_radio_072; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 11)
  - President Eisenhower report on first 7 months in office and first session of 83rd Congress (both sides), 08/06/1953; wsyr_radio_414; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower returns from "Summit" at Geneva; President Eisenhower departure Address for Geneva Summit, 07/15/1954; 07/25/1955; wsyr_radio_423; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower speech before NY Republicans (parts 1 and 2), wsyr_radio_415; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower Speech Before the United Nations, 12/08/1953; wsyr_radio_074; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 12)
  - President Eisenhower speech of Monday (parts 1 and 2), 04/05/1954; wsyr_radio_419; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower speech on Korean truce, John Foster Dulles on Korean Truce; Korean truce - UN and Washington reaction, 07/27/1953; wsyr_radio_413; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower State of the Nation speech (parts 1 and 3), 01/07/1954; wsyr_radio_417; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower State of the Nation speech (parts 2 and 4), 01/07/1954; wsyr_radio_418; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Eisenhower, Milwaukee, WI. - Foreign and domestic issues, parts 1 and 2, 06/10/1953; wsyr_radio_067; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 10)
    A - President Eisenhower Address before the 33rd Convention of the U. S. Junior Chamber of Commerce (JC's). Introduced by JC's President Horace E. Henderson
  - President Eisenhower: Future Farmers Address, parts 1 and 2, 10/10/1953; 10/15/1953; wsyr_radio_073; at Kansas City, Missouri; dubbed from tape; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 11)
  - President Ford (9:30-9:48 PM) (part 2), 08/12/1974; wsyr_radio_996; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 18:00 (Box 57)
  - President Ford Address to Joint Session of Congress (9-9:30 PM), 08/12/1974; wsyr_radio_995; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:00 (Box 57)
  - President Ford attempted shooting, wsyr_radio_599; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
    Other NBC network activity news: Medicare; L. A. Tread Contract; Restoration of H2O in Trenton, N. J.; Hoffa Disappears; 1st class mail price increase
  - President H. S. Truman - Joint session of Congress (parts 1 and 3), 01/04/1950; wsyr_radio_367; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Harry S. Truman address, 05/14/1950; wsyr_radio_369; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Harry S. Truman Joint Session at Congress, part 2 of 3, 01/04/1950; wsyr_radio_052; Side B blank; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 9)
  - President Ike [Eisenhower] on defense of budget (parts 1 and 2), 05/14/1957; wsyr_radio_425; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Ike [Eisenhower] on defense of budget (parts 1 and 2), 05/21/1957; wsyr_radio_426; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Kennedy - Cuba Crisis Talk to Nation; Excerpt Press Conference, 11/20/1962; wsyr_radio_971; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
  - President Nixon - Final Address From White House, August 9, 1974; wsyr_radio_994; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 57)
  - President Nixon (7:30-7:56 PM), 11/07/1973; wsyr_radio_988; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:00 (Box 57)
  - President Nixon Address on Watergate Tapes (9:35 PM), 04/29/1974; wsyr_radio_992; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 57)
  - President Nixon Addresses the Nation on Viet Nam [misspelled Naum] (10 PM), 04/26/1972; wsyr_radio_977; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
  - President Nixon from Camp David. Finance Committee for the Reelection of the President [CREEP], 10/22/1972; wsyr_radio_982; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
  - President Nixon Speech to the Russian People (12 noon to 12:22:55 PM), 07/02/1974; wsyr_radio_993; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 22:55 (Box 57)
  - President Nixon: Fourth of July Address, 07/04/1972; wsyr_radio_980; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 12:45 (Box 56)
  - President Nixon’s Viet Nam Address, 05/08/1972; wsyr_radio_978; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
  - President of the U.S.A. [Eisenhower] - Security (missiles) parts 1 and 2, 11/07/1957; wsyr_radio_096; Radio and television address: National security - military initiative; closes with National Anthem.; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 15)
  - President Roosevelt - Message to Congress (parts 2 and 4); ;Organ Music; Circus of Science (interviews and demos); Hawaiian music program, 09/21/1939; wsyr_radio_106; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Roosevelt - Message to Congress, # 2; Inside test cut - organ music; Roosevelt - Message to Congress, # 4; next 3 cuts: Circus of science - interviews and demos; Santa; Part of Hawaiian music program
  - President Roosevelt - "1st Day of War", 09/03/1939; wsyr_radio_113; Lacquer discs/acetates
    handwritten note reads: "Roosevelt, Sept. 3, 1939. Cue - "I have said that again and again". First - "I hope that the US will keep out of war". End - "No black out peace in US out. 40 sec."
  - President Roosevelt - "3rd Term Inauguration" (part 1), 01/20/1941; wsyr_radio_150; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - "3rd Term Inauguration" (part 2); Raymond Gram swing, 01/20/1941; wsyr_radio_151; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - "Fireside chat - Unlimited Emergency" (part 2); "Maxwell House - Coffee time" (part 2), 05/27/1941; 05/29/1941; wsyr_radio_153; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - "Fireside chat - Unlimited Emergency" (parts 1 and 3), 05/27/1941; wsyr_radio_152; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - "Message - War on Japan" (part 1 and 3), 12/07/1941; 12/08/1941; wsyr_radio_163; note on unlabeled side reads: "NBC House of Representative seems to be after 12/7/41".; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - "Message to Congress on War on Japan" (part 1); Lang Thompson Orchestra (part 2), 12/03/1941; 12/04/1941; 12/09/1941; wsyr_radio_165; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - "Message to Congress on War on Japan" (part 2); Lang Thompson Orchestra (part 1), 12/03/1941; 12/09/1941; wsyr_radio_166; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - "Message to Congress on War on Japan" (part 2); Prime Minister Churchill - Regarding US declaring war on Japan (part 1), 12/08/1941; wsyr_radio_164; note reads: "Churchill, No. 1, Dec. 8, ‘41 - first words: "In view of the attack and this declaration". End - "Have been giving [?]. Pass ports...".; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Address Canadian Parliament (part 2); President Roosevelt launches National War Fund Drive, 08/25/1943; wsyr_radio_239; includes NBC chimes; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Birthday Ball; Vadeboncoeur and H. R. Eakins, 01/29/1944; 02/20/1944; wsyr_radio_219; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Coal strike talk (part 1); Richard Harkness News, 05/02/1943; wsyr_radio_197; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Coal strike talk (part 2); Richard Harkness News, 05/02/1943; 05/03/1943; 05/06/1943; wsyr_radio_198; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Declaration of War on Germany and Italy, 12/11/1941; wsyr_radio_167; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Historical file (part 2 and 4), 03/01/1945; wsyr_radio_261; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Historical file (parts 1 and 3), 03/01/1945; wsyr_radio_260; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Jefferson Memorial; Bond Buyers, 04/12/1943; 04/13/1943; wsyr_radio_201; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Labor Day (part 2); "One man’s family" (part 1) (CH10 BK 43); Colonel Lindbergh - First speech on war, 09/07/1942; 09/03/1942; 09/15/1939; wsyr_radio_182; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Message to Congress (Part 1 and 3), 09/21/1939; wsyr_radio_110; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Message to Congress (part 1); "Hidden stars" - Bonnie Baker and Orrin Tucker (part 1), 01/06/1941; wsyr_radio_147; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Message to Congress (part 2), 01/06/1941; wsyr_radio_148; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Message to Congress (part 3), 01/06/1941; wsyr_radio_149; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Report on war (part 2), 02/23/1942; wsyr_radio_175; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Report on war (parts 1 and 3), 02/23/1942; wsyr_radio_174; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Return from the Pacific (part 2), 08/12/1944; wsyr_radio_230; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Return from the Pacific (parts 1 and 3), 08/12/1944; wsyr_radio_229; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Rome campaign; King George VI - Invasion Day message, NBC (#6), 06/05/1944; 06/06/1944; wsyr_radio_223; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - State of the Nation (part 1), 01/06/1945; wsyr_radio_263; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - State of the Nation (part 2 and 4), 01/07/1943; wsyr_radio_212; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - State of the Nation (part 2); President Roosevelt: Christmas Message, 12/24/1944; 01/06/1945; wsyr_radio_236; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - State of the Nation (parts 1 and 3), 01/07/1943; wsyr_radio_211; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt - Youth talk (part 3), 09/03/1942; wsyr_radio_181; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (part 1 and 2), 06/12/1944; wsyr_radio_227; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (part 1); "Here’s to youth" (part 1), 12/24/1943; 01/15/1944; wsyr_radio_187; NBC, first show of series, file 14; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (part 1); "One mans family" (Chapter 13 Book 40) (part 2), 12/28/1941; 01/06/1942; wsyr_radio_171; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (part 2); Lynn Cramer - Vandencoeur interview, 01/26/1942; 01/06/1942; wsyr_radio_172; also contains a cut at end on "happy landings"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (part 2); Secretary of War Stimson discusses National Service Act, NBC with chimes, 12/24/1943; wsyr_radio_188; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (part 2); Sports News; [illegible] Men’s shop stores, Marliand [sp?] interview, Wally and Jane show, 01/08/1944; 01/10/1944; wsyr_radio_218; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (part 3); "Information Please" (part 1), 09/11/1941; 08/29/1941; wsyr_radio_160; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (parts 1 and 3), 09/11/1941; wsyr_radio_159; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt (parts 1 and 3); Club 570 promos, 01/10/1944; wsyr_radio_217; note reads: "3 inside cuts. Club 570 - promos; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt Armistice Day Speech. Olivio Santoro complete, 11/11/1942; wsyr_radio_017; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
  - President Roosevelt on NBC (18-19 Yr. Old Draftees); Songs for a Soldier; Ripley - Voice Tracks and bridges, 10/12/1942; wsyr_radio_007; note on sleeve: "Ruth Chilton’s Matinee"; President Roosevelt NBC 10:00 PM #1 of 2: 18-19 Yr Old Draftees; Songs for a Soldier - Ripley - Voice Tracks & Bridges; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 1)
    A-1: Radio address (1 of 2); B-1: Intro for "On the alert"; B-2: Spot for Carling Red. Cop ale and intro for "Conchito Lopez; B-3: Thoughts on saying good-bye in WW2, intro for "Your flag and mine."
  - President Roosevelt speech (part 1 and 3), 02/12/1943; wsyr_radio_214; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt speech (part 2); "Funny money man", 02/12/1943; wsyr_radio_215; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Note reads: " WSYR 2:30 pm a "Let’s make a deal" type". There is a torn Inserted note in the sleeve, what is left reads: "... starting works are (we are). Time about 40 sec. End - Stavery & War. Short pause".
  - President Roosevelt speech; Marching with the Marines, 02/22/1943; 02/27/1943; wsyr_radio_203; note on sleeve reads: "Minister of Finland"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Roosevelt, part 2: 18-19 year old Boy - National Anthem (incomplete), 10/12/1942; wsyr_radio_019; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 6)
  - President Roosevelt, part 3 "State of the Union" Message to Congress; "One Man’s Family", part 1, Chapter 13, Book 40, 01/06/1942; wsyr_radio_011; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 1)
    Roosevelt Pt III "State of the Union" Message to Congress; One Mans Family - Red Part 1 Ch 13 BK 40, sponsor Tender leaf Tea. War time themed - civilian contributions to help war effort (New Year Eve celebration). Candy story (close)
  - President Roosevelt; "One Man’s Family", Chapter 10, Book 43, part 2 of 2, 09/07/1942; wsyr_radio_008; President Roosevelt NBC 9:30 PM #1 of 2; One Mans Family Off Red Part II Ch10 BK43 [crossed out]; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 1)
    A-1: Fragment re: wartime metal shortage; President Roosevelt (part 1); "One Man’s Family" (Part 2, Chapter 10, Book 43), sponsor "Fleischmann's yeast"
  - President Roosevelt: 3rd War Loan Drive; Songs for a Soldier(Voice tracks and Bridges), 09/08/1943; wsyr_radio_021; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 3)
    A-1: James Cagney - S. A. G. President for a play "Back the attack with war bonds"; A-2: President Roosevelt radio address - "3rd War loan drive"; B-1: Song's for a soldier (WSYR program); B-2: Carlings black label beer (spot, song intro); B-3: Talk about war effort and song intro (WSYR announcer)
  - President Roosevelt: Report On War, part 2; Bess Johnson, 04/28/1942; wsyr_radio_009; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 1)
    President Roosevelt: Report On War (part 2); The story of Bess Johnson, sponsor "Super Side", "Colgate tooth powder".
  - President Roosevelt: Report On War, parts 1 and 3, 04/28/1942; wsyr_radio_010; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 1)
    Over (grisly mention); Roosevelt End of _ with NBC ID & Chimes. B-Part 2 closes with Truman Bradley making an announcement re: Red Skelton show and President Roosevelt (incomplete fragment)
  - President Statement on Viet Nam Withdraw Read by Ron Nessel with Questions and Answers by Henry Kissinger, 04/29/1975; wsyr_radio_998; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - President Truman Speech to Congress - Steel strike; [unknown], 06/10/1952; wsyr_radio_406; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Note on sleeve reads: "Five of the best for Sun. June 8. Tr. 1 - Gove; 2 - Doubleday; tr. 3 - Murphy; tr. 4 - Deline; tr. 5 - O’Donnell".
  - President Truman - A. D. A. [Americans for Democratic Action?] speech; [unknown], 07/17/1952; wsyr_radio_402; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Civil Defense - General MacArthur (parts 1 and 2), 05/07/1951; wsyr_radio_382; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Close San Francisco conference (part 1); Big Three Conference, 06/25/1945; 08/02/1945; wsyr_radio_241; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Close San Francisco conference (part 2); President Truman on Berlin Conference (part 2), 06/25/1945; wsyr_radio_242; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Inflation (part 1), 06/14/1951; wsyr_radio_383; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Message to Congress (part 2), 05/25/1946; wsyr_radio_308a; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Message to opening of Congres (part 2), wsyr_radio_341; starts w/ "42% ", re: Price inflation wage earners farm prices. Combating inflation - economics, 1947"; ends w/ "might not recover" and listing of goods; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Ottawa speech (part 3), 06/11/1947; wsyr_radio_334; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Ottawa speech (parts 1 and 2), 06/11/1947; wsyr_radio_333; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Press Association (part 1); Reunion of 35th Division (part 1), 04/21/1947; 06/07/1947; wsyr_radio_331; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Press Association (part 2); Reunion of 35th Division (part 2), 04/21/1947; 06/07/1947; wsyr_radio_332; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - speech to regiment; [unknown], 06/07/1952; wsyr_radio_405; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - State of the Nation (part 2); Pet Milk (part 2), 01/05/1949; wsyr_radio_353; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - State of the Nation (parts 1 and 3), 01/05/1949; wsyr_radio_352; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - State of the union message to Congress (part 1 and 3), 01/07/1948; wsyr_radio_342; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - State of the union message to Congress (part 2), 01/07/1948; wsyr_radio_343; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - State of Union Message to Congress (parts 1 and 3), 01/09/1952; wsyr_radio_392; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman - Steel crisis (parts 1 and 2), 04/07/1952; wsyr_radio_401; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Notes on sleeve read: "For Ernie Cuno. Cut 1 - Deacon Doubleday; cut 2 - Bill Rothrum; cut 3 - Mayor Corcoran; Cut 4 - Murphy. Bob: Put Murph’s on here too - then pls put on my desk."
  - President Truman (part 1 and 3), 10/27/1945; wsyr_radio_289; label on side 1 is damaged; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 1 and 3), 12/15/1950; wsyr_radio_376; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 1), 10/24/1947; wsyr_radio_339; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 1), 03/17/1948; wsyr_radio_347; note on label reads: "Used AM 3/13/1948"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 1), 07/19/1950; wsyr_radio_370; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 2), 10/27/1945; wsyr_radio_290; label on side 2 is damaged; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 2), 07/19/1950; wsyr_radio_371; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 2), 12/15/1950; wsyr_radio_377; side 2 has no label; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 2), 01/08/1951; wsyr_radio_379; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 2) (#11); Goes calling on Mrs. Breuman, Mattydale (part 2, program 77), 03/12/1947; wsyr_radio_328; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (part 2); [unknown], 10/24/1947; wsyr_radio_340; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman (parts 1 and 3), 01/08/1951; wsyr_radio_378; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman [State of the] Union Message, part 2, 01/09/1952; wsyr_radio_093; dubbed from tape; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 14)
  - President Truman address, 05/14/1950; wsyr_radio_368; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman address at Jefferson Memorial expansion in University of Missouri–St. Louis, parts 1 and 2, 06/10/1950; wsyr_radio_049; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 8)
  - President Truman Address to the Joint Session of the Congress, part 2 [and partial 3], 03/17/1948; wsyr_radio_054; Side B-blank; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 9)
  - President Truman at Baylor University, Texas (part 1); President Truman talk - Labor Bill, 03/06/1947; 06/20/1947; wsyr_radio_335; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman at Baylor University, Texas (part 2), 03/06/1947; wsyr_radio_326; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman at Monticello (incomplete), 07/04/1947; wsyr_radio_336; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman at opening UN General Assembly, New York (part 1), 10/23/1946; wsyr_radio_323; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman at opening UN General Assembly, New York (part 2), 10/23/1946; wsyr_radio_324; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman at University of California (part 1); President Truman message to Congress (part 2), 06/12/1948; 07/27/1948; wsyr_radio_349; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman awarding 100th Congressional medal to Sargent Jake W. Lindsey; VE Day show - United Nations salute (part 2), 05/02/1945; 05/21/1945; wsyr_radio_249; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman comes home (part 1), 11/05/1948; wsyr_radio_351; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman from Brazil - (part 1 (11); 11 PM Breaks - For Sunday [illegible], 08/31/1947; 09/02/1947; wsyr_radio_337; Lacquer discs/acetates
    1 - D’Simas wid BRR; 2 - Heaphy at Son; 3 - Cordal Manor
  - President Truman from Brazil (part 2);[unknown], 09/02/1947; wsyr_radio_338; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman from Mexico City; [unknown] (part 1), 03/03/1947; wsyr_radio_325; damaged label on side 2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman Jefferson Jackson Day dinner (parts 1 and 2), 03/29/1952; wsyr_radio_400; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman message to Congress on railroad. Strike (part 2), 05/25/1946; wsyr_radio_307; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman on Railroad Strike, 05/24/1946; wsyr_radio_306; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman on Reconversion, wsyr_radio_291; labels are damaged; Lacquer discs/acetates
    President Truman speech (evening) Exec. Order 9599 (War to Peace transition) Reconvertion. Cut inside out, ends w/"allowed at a particular time". Side without label. Part 2 on the labeled side ends w/ National Anthem & NBC chimes
  - President Truman on Reconvertion [sic], Part 2 (#10), 10/30/1945; wsyr_radio_292; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - President Truman Part 2 of 2, wsyr_radio_294; label is damaged; Lacquer discs/acetates
    President Truman - Stabilization, ?/14/1946, Part 2 of 2. Dan Pando closes with NBC chimes
  - President Truman preparedness speech - address at Washington Monument, Memorial grounds (part 1 and 2), 07/04/1951; wsyr_radio_385; Lacquer discs/acetates